Finding Aid for the North American New Music Festival Sound Recordings, 1983-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
North American New Music Festival Sound Recordings, 1983-1993
Mus. Arc. 13.1
North American New Music Festival (Buffalo, N.Y.)
10 boxes ( 390 cassettes, 22 reels and 1 container with 2 hard drives and accompanying documentation )
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Contains sound recordings on 390 cassettes and 22 reels of performances from the North American New Music Festival, a series of annual festivals of contemporary art music sponsored by the University at Buffalo Department of Music from 1983 to 1993. The collection contains recordings of circa 720 musical works composed by about 334 different composers, including most of the most prominent composers of the 20th century. Many works were rehearsed and prepared with their respective composers in attendance and performers at the festival were chiefly specialists in new music.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
The cassettes in the collection were copied circa 1996 from the originals held by the Music Department sound engineer. The reels were acquired from radio station WNED in Buffalo in 2017.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
The original recordings were made on cassettes. The contents were digitized onto hard drives. Preservation wav files were created to match the original cassette and reel faces. Digital files for the cassette are named with roots that match the tape numbering, for example ubmu0013_1_001a is the root file name for the digital files derived from Cassette 001 Side A. The digital files for the reels are numbered sequentially to follow the cassette numbering (digital files for cassettes are numbered 001-390; digital files for the reels are numbered 391-412). For the cassettes, service copies were created directly from the preservation masters. For the reels, intermediate Production master files were created to match the content, one file per musical work or spoken word segment. Service copies were derived from the Production masters.
Historical Note
The North American New Music Festival was founded in 1983 by pianist/composerYvar Mikhashoff and percussionist Jan Williams, faculty members of the University at Buffalo Music Department and dedicated proponents of contemporary and avant-garde art music. Their aim was to produce, over a ten-day period, a concentrated series of concerts and related events at multiple Buffalo-area locations. These annual music festivals featured a wide range of modern musical styles composed and performed both by emerging creative musicians and by established composers of national and international reputation.
The Festivals were held in March or April in the years between 1983 and 1992, in October of 1993. Events took place in more than a dozen locations, including concert halls, art galleries, churches, theaters, and cabarets.
Scope and Content Note
Contains sound recordings on 390 cassettes and 22 reels of performances from the North American New Music Festival, a series of annual festivals of contemporary art music sponsored by the University at Buffalo Department of Music from 1983 to 1993. The collection contains recordings of circa 720 musical works composed by about 334 different composers, including most of the most prominent composers of the 20th century. Many works were rehearsed and prepared with their respective composers in attendance and the performers at the festival were chiefly specialists in new music. The works of more than 300 composers were presented, including many world premieres. In addition to the 720 musical works recorded, an additional 217 works were performed but not recorded.
Arrangement
Arranged into three series:
I. Cassettes
II. Reel-to-reel tapes
III. Hard drives and accompanying documentation
Container List
- Cassettes, 1983-1993, I.; Cassette 1-390
  The sequence of 390 cassettes represents the principal portion of the collection, spanning the first concert in 1983 through the 200th and final concert in 1993.
  Arranged numerically by cassette number and listed by cassette sides. The numbering also reflects a chronological order.
  - Sullivan, Kenneth Prima volta (1982), 1983-04-05, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 001 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 001 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 001, April 5, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 17:53
    Performers: Marlene Witnauer, flute; Edward Yadzinski, clarinet; Richard Myers, trombone; Marc Wooldridge, percussion; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Takeshi Mineta, violoncello; Jan Williams, conductor
    Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo)
    Buffalo premiere
    Digitized copies:
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_001aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_001asc.mp3
  - Lohn, Jeffrey Music for two pianos (1982), 1983-04-05, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 002 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 001 Side b)
    Duration: 25:02
    Performers: Anthony de Mare, Michael McCandless, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_001bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_001bsc.mp3
  - Smit, Leo, 1921-1999 Academic graffiti (rev. 1982), 1983-04-05, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 003 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 002 Side a)
    Duration: 09:57
    Performers: Gary Burgess, tenor; Allen Sigel, clarinet; Carlo Pinto, piano; Robert Hausmann, violoncello; Jan Williams, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_002aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_002asc.mp3
  - Foss, Lukas, 1922-2009 Solo observed (1982), 1983-04-05, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 004 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 002 Side b)
    Duration: 16:17
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Michael McCandless, electric organ; Robert Hausmann, violoncello; Jan Williams, percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_002bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_002bsc.mp3
  - Copland, Aaron, 1900-1990 El salon Mexico (1946/1983), 1983-04-05, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 005 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 003 Side a)
    Duration: 13:27
    Performers: James Pyne, clarinet; Darlene Jussila, bassoon; David Kuehn, trumpet; Donald Miller, trombone; Jan Williams, percussion; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Thomas Halpin, violin; Nicholas Molfese, bass
    Arranged by Yvar Mikhashoff; world premiere.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_003aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_003asc.mp3
  - McLean, Barton, 1938- Ixtlan for two pianos (1982), 1983-04-06, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 006 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 003 Side b)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 002, April 6, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 15:28
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, Michael McCandless, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_003bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_003bsc.mp3
  - Johnston, Ben Suite for microtonal piano (1978), 1983-04-07, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 007 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 004 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 003, April 7, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 17:04
    Performers: John Rinehart, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_004aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_004asc.mp3
  - Johnston, Ben Quartet, strings, no. 4 (1973), 1983-04-07, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 008 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 004 Side b)
    Duration: 12:48
    Performers: Tremont Quartet
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_004bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_004bsc.mp3
  - Johnston, Ben In memory, Harry Partch (1975), 1983-04-07, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 009 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 005 Side a)
    Duration: 22:17
    Performers: Martha, Herr, soprano; UB Percussion Ensemble; Compass Players; tape
    Buffalo premiere; First movement not recorded: tape only (?)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_005aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_005asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Sonata, clarinet alone (1933), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 010 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 005 Side b)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 004, April 8, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 05:03
    Performers: James Perone, clarinet
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_005bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_005bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John Music for wind instruments (1938), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 011 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 006 Side a)
    Duration: 10:30
    Performers: Compass Players
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_006aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_006asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Wonderful widow of eighteen springs (1942), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 012 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 006 Side b)
    Duration: 03:30
    Performers: Martha Herr, soprano; Michael McCandless, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_006bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_006bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John Imaginary landscape no. 3 (1942), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 013 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 007 Side a)
    Duration: 04:17
    Performers: UB Percussion Ensemble
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_007aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_007asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Credo in us (1942), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 014 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 007 Side b)
    Duration: 15:43
    Performers: UB Percussion ensemble
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_007bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_007bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John She is asleep (1943), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 015 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 008 Side a)
    Duration: 16:55
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_008aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_008asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Nocturne (1947), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 016 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 008 Side b)
    Duration: 05:51
    Performers: Thomas Halpin, violin; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_008bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_008bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John Suite for toy piano (1948), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 017 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 009 Side a)
    Duration: 08:21
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_009aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_009asc.mp3
  - Cage, John In a landscape (1948), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 018 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 009 Side b)
    Duration: 08:33
    Performers: Mario Falcao, harp
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_009bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_009bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John Six melodies (1950), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 019 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 010 Side a)
    Duration: 14:15
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_010aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_010asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Concerto for prepared piano and orchestra (1951), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 020 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 010 Side b)
    Duration: 24:17
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Compass Players, Jan Williams, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_010bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_010bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John 27'10.554" for a percussionist / 45' for a speaker (1956), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 021 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_100 (Box 1, Audiocassette 011 Side a)
    Duration: 46:09
    Performers: Jan Williams, percussion; John Cage, speaker
    Two compositions performed simultaneously
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_011aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_011asc.mp3
  - Cage, John Music walk (1958), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 022 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_100 (Box 1, Audiocassette 011 Side b)
    Duration: 11:44
    Performers: Michael McCandless and assistants
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_011bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_011bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John Cheap imitation (1977), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 023 Tape type: TDK_SA-90 (Box 1, Audiocassette 012 Side a)
    Duration: 34:28
    Performers: Thomas Halpin, violin
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_012aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_012asc.mp3
  - Cage, John 49 waltzes for Buffalo (1977-1983), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 024 Tape type: TDK_SA-90 (Box 1, Audiocassette 012 Side b)
    Duration: 04:13
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_012bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_012bsc.mp3
  - Cage, John Litany for the whale (1980), 1983-04-08, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 025 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 013 Side a)
    Duration: 27:00
    Performers: Martha Herr, Jocelyn Alaimo, sopranos
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_013aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_013asc.mp3
  - Brant, Henry, 1913-2008 Hand organ music (1933), 1983-04-09, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 026 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 013 Side b)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 005, April 9, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 03:23
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, Henry Brant, piano
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_013bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_013bsc.mp3
  - Brant, Henry, 1913-2008 All souls carnival (1949), 1983-04-09, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 027 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 014 Side a)
    Duration: 17:14
    Performers: Marlene Witnauer, piccolo; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; Henry Brant, organ; Thomas Halpin, violin; Bruce Cramer, violoncello
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_014aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_014asc.mp3
  - Brant, Henry, 1913-2008 Percussion symphony (1951), 1983-04-09, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 028 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 014 Side b)
    Duration: 31:22
    Performers: UB Percussion Ensemble, Henry Brant, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_014bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_014bsc.mp3
  - Brant, Henry, 1913-2008 Horizontals extending (1982), 1983-04-09, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 029 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 015 Side a)
    Duration: 11:40
    Performers: UB Wind Ensemble, Bruce Penner, conductor
    World premiere; Pre-performance talk by Brant
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_015aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_015asc.mp3
  - Brant, Henry, 1913-2008 Inside track (1982), 1983-04-09, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 030 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 015 Side b)
    Duration: 17:20
    Performers: Yvar Mikhashoff, piano; University Philharmonia, Henry Brant, conductor
    U.S. premiere
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_015bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_015bsc.mp3
  - Schafer, R. Murray Quartet, strings, no. 2 ("Waves") (1979), 1983-04-10, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 031 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 016 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 006, April 10, 1983, 3:00 p.m.
    Duration: 24:10
    Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo)
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_016aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_016asc.mp3
  - Schafer, R. Murray Crown of Ariadne (1979), 1983-04-10, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 032 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 016 Side b)
    Duration: 21:55
    Performers: Mario Falcao, harp and percussion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_016bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_016bsc.mp3
  - Schafer, R. Murray La testa d'Adriane (1978), 1983-04-10, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 033 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 017 Side a)
    Duration: 14:01
    Performers: Martha Herr, soprano; Joe Macerollo, free bass accordion
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_017aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_017asc.mp3
  - La Barbara, Joan, 1947- October music: Star showers and extraterrestrials(1980), 1983-04-10, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 034 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 017 Side b)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 007, April 10, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 14:59
    Performers: Joan La Barbara, amplified voice; tape
    Albright-Knox Art Gallery
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_017bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_017bsc.mp3
  - Subotnick, Morton Last dream of the beast (1979), 1983-04-10, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 035 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 018 Side a)
    Duration: 16:16
    Performers: Joan La Barbara, voice; tape
    Side b is blank
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_018aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_018asc.mp3
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Three voices (1980). Part 1, 1983-04-10, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 036 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 1, Audiocassette 019 Side a)
    Duration: 45:50
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_019aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_019asc.mp3
  - Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987 Three voices (1980). Part 2, 1983-04-10, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 036 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 1, Audiocassette 019 Side b)
    Duration: 45:24
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_019bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_019bsc.mp3
  - Vigeland, Nils Second trio (1983), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 036A Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 020 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 008, April 11, 1983, 12:15 p.m.
    Duration: 08:42
    Performers: Thomas Halpin, violin; Jan Williams, percussion; Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    Buffalo and Erie County Public Library (N.Y.)
    World premiere; repeated performance on Tape 22a. Preceded by spoken introduction by Yvar Mikhashoff.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_020aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_020asc.mp3
  - Gena, Peter McKinley (1983), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 036B Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 020 Side b)
    Duration: 13:13
    World premiere; repeated performance on Tape 22b. Preceded by spoken introduction by Yvar Mikhashoff.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_020bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_020bsc.mp3
  - Di Pietro, Rocco Three aerials (1972), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 036C Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 021 Side a)
    Duration: 12:00
    Performers: Thomas Halpin, violin; Jan Williams, percussion, Yvar Mikhashoff, piano
    World premiere; repeated performance on Tape 23a. Preceded by spoken introduction by Yvar Mikhashoff.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_021aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_021asc.mp3
  - Brant, Henry, 1913-2008 Music for a five-and-dime store (1932), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 036D Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 021 Side b)
    Duration: 05:19
    Repeated performance on Tape 23b. Preceded by spoken introduction by Yvar Mikhashoff.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_021bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_021bsc.mp3
  - Vigeland, Nils Second trio (1983), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 036E Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 022 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 009, April 11, 1983, 1:15 p.m.
    Duration: 09:27
    Repeat performance of Tape 20a. Preceded by spoken introduction by Yvar Mikhashoff.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_022aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_022asc.mp3
  - Gena, Peter McKinley (1983), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 036F Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 022 Side b)
    Duration: 12:10
    Repeat performance of Tape 20b one hour later. Preceded by spoken introduction by Yvar Mikhashoff.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_022bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_022bsc.mp3
  - Di Pietro, Rocco Three aerials (1972), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 036G Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 023 Side a)
    Duration: 13:35
    Repeat performance of Tape 21a one hour later. Preceded by spoken introduction by Yvar Mikhashoff.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_023aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_023asc.mp3
  - Brant, Henry, 1913-2008 Music for a five-and-dime store (1932), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 036H Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 023 Side b)
    Duration: 05:25
    Repeat performance of Tape 21b one hour later. Preceded by spoken introduction by Yvar Mikhashoff.
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_023bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_023bsc.mp3
  - Chadwick, G. W. (George Whitefield), 1854-1931 Quartet, strings, no. 3, D major (1885), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 037 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 024 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 010, April 11, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 24:22
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_024aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_024asc.mp3
  - Chadwick, G. W. (George Whitefield), 1854-1931 Quartet, strings, no. 4, E minor (1896), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 038 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 024 Side b)
    Duration: 29:49
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_024bam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_024bsc.mp3
  - Chadwick, G. W. (George Whitefield), 1854-1931 Quintet, piano, strings (1888), 1983-04-11, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 039 Tape type: TDK_SA_90 (Box 1, Audiocassette 025 Side a)
    Duration: 38:13
    Performers: Stephen Manes, piano; Tremont Quartet
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_025aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_025asc.mp3
  - Austin, Larry Canadian coastlines (1981), 1983-04-12, 1 audiocassette; Original cassette numbering: NAF 040 Tape type: TDK_SA-X_60 (Box 1, Audiocassette 026 Side a)
    North American New Music Festival Concert 011, April 12, 1983, 8:00 p.m.
    Duration: 10:50
    Performers: Compass Players, Bruce Penner, conductor
    Preservation archival master file: ubmu0013_1_026aam.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0013_1_026asc.mp3